<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="F:\mutuallyExclusiveReality.com\xml\rss.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">
	<channel>
		<title>News Hounds</title>
		<link>http://www.newshounds.us/</link>
		<description>We watch FOX so you don&apos;t have to.</description>
		<dc:language>en-us</dc:language>
		<dc:creator>newshounds@gmail.com</dc:creator>
		<dc:date>2005-04-06T20:54:44-05:00</dc:date>
		<admin:generatorAgent rdf:resource="http://www.movabletype.org/?v=3.121"/>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<sy:updateBase>2000-01-01T12:00+00:00</sy:updateBase>
		<item>
			<title>Fox has a new expression - &apos;We&apos;ve Been Told.....&apos;</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/06/fox_has_a_new_expression_weve_been_told.php</link>
			<description>Today on Studio B with Shepard Smith the coverage was wall to wall about the Pope. But not exactly the Pope, the coverage seemed to be focused on the crowds outside. Endless shots of the crowds of people as Smith delivered his show while walking alongside of them. Smith managed to take a break from the crowds to do an interview with Frank Gaffney, former Assistant Secretary of State. Smith asked Gaffney if the selection of a Kurd as the new President of Iraq was a uniting or divisive move and Gaffney went into a diatribe of &apos;we&apos;ve been told....&apos;...</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5813@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Studio B</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-06T20:54:44-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A Monument to George Bush at the Vatican?</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/06/a_monument_to_george_bush_at_the_vatican.php</link>
			<description>Today, on Your World w/Neil Cavuto, Fox&apos;s Greg Burke opened a report from Rome with this sentence: &quot;Well, you know, we used to always joke here that if it weren&apos;t for the Iraq war, they&apos;d probably build a monument to George Bush in the Vatican gardens.&quot; Comment: This is a tiny example of the kind of thing the Fox News viewer is hearing again and again this week. Wait a day or two; by the time Bush returns from Rome, he&apos;ll probably be the new pope....</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5812@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Cavuto/&amp; Your World</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-06T19:35:45-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>On FNC, &quot;Four&quot; Equals &quot;Vast&quot;</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/06/on_fnc_four_equals_vast.php</link>
			<description>Last night (4/5) on Special Report, Brit Hume used his one-on-one interview segment to promote a new book by Byron York, &quot;The Vast Left-Wing Conspiracy&quot;....</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5811@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Special Report w/Brit Hume</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-06T15:33:43-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Fox&apos;s  Big Story thankfully all Poped out</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/06/foxs_big_story_thankfully_all_poped_out.php</link>
			<description>The Big Story with John Gibson today 4/5/05 spent only 7 minutes on the solemnities concerning the Pope&apos;s death. They were back to shallow reporting and skimming important-looking topics but the important news of the day, the Big Story, did not materialize....</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5810@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Big Story w/John Gibson</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-06T01:41:01-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A Few Minutes To Discuss Tom DeLay&apos;s Multiple Corruption Scandals</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/06/a_few_minutes_to_discuss_tom_delays_multiple_corruption_scandals.php</link>
			<description>Monday night, I chastised John Gibson for spending five minutes on Michael Jackson&apos;s trial and zero time on the Tom DeLay scandals (notice the plural). So I have to praise Alan Colmes for bringing up on his FOX News radio show two new corruption scandals involving Tom DeLay last night, brief as the discussion was....</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5809@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Alan Colmes on the Radio</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-06T01:40:16-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Trying To Paint The Pope Republican</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/05/trying_to_paint_the_pope_republican.php</link>
			<description>If you thought FOX News&apos; pandering to the Schindler family was disgraceful, you&apos;ll probably turn apoplectic over the &quot;Real Journalism, Fair and Balanced&quot; network&apos;s efforts to portray Pope John Paul II as soulmate and confederate of Ronald Reagan....</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5807@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>FOXNEWS.com</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-05T23:20:04-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Brief Glimpses of News Other than the Pope</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/05/brief_glimpses_of_news_other_than_the_pope.php</link>
			<description>On Studio B with Shepard Smith today, Smith is, of course, in Vatican City. We are treated to many pictures of crowds, crowds and more crowds. Maybe if they threw in some art or something, they could keep it interesting (no disrespect intended). Studio B managed to cover some other stories - in &apos;small&apos; doses only....</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5806@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Studio B</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-05T23:06:38-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>In Their Eyes Still Hanoi Jane</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/05/in_their_eyes_still_hanoi_jane.php</link>
			<description>Hannity and Michael Reagan were unable to summon Christian forgiveness for Jane Fonda who recently published a memoir, My Life So Far where she expressed regret for her trip to Hanoi during the Vietnam war. When Colmes and Bob Beckel joined the mix defending Fonda, Michael Reagan became unglued actually screaming on air. 4/05/05...</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5808@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Hannity &amp; Colmes</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-05T22:36:25-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>God, Morals, and Money</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/05/god_morals_and_money.php</link>
			<description>As Your World w/Neil Cavuto began today (April 5, 2005), I started to get the feeling I&apos;d accidentally turned to a religious channel. The show opened with a ten minute roundtable featuring five Catholic businessmen (six, if you count Cavuto who was raised a Catholic). The segment was titled: &quot;Ultimate Chief Executive.&quot; Next came Bill Simon, conservative millionaire and a former California gubernatorial candidate. He swooned over his faith and his pope. A few minutes later I endured a second roundtable titled, &quot;Moral Money Makers,&quot; and after that I listened to Lee Iacocca talk about meeting not one, but two...</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5805@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Cavuto/&amp; Your World</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-05T18:29:05-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Smells &amp; Bells</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/05/smells_bells.php</link>
			<description>Today (4/5) FNL gave only a minimal obligatory nod to the Pope, with Greg Burke reporting on the &quot;mess&quot; in Rome &amp; cleverly saying that &quot;some&quot; call all the pageantry &quot;smells &amp; bells&quot; -- the standard Fox ploy of attributing a snide remark to the elusive &quot;some&quot; who allegedly say it. Brigitte Quinn &amp; David Asman went into paroxysms about Peter Jennings having lung cancer. The only thing that diverted their attention from Jennings was a classic car chase in Los Angeles, to which they devoted nearly the last 18 minutes of the program -- without even an ad break!...</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5804@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Fox News Live</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-05T16:21:08-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>&quot;One World&quot; Concept, According to FNC</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/05/one_world_concept_according_to_fnc.php</link>
			<description>I had my VCR set to tape the replay of Special Report last night (4/4), but what I got instead was an hour in the middle of Rick Folbaum &amp; Heather Nauert co-anchoring a special on the Pope (&quot;The Death of Pope John Paul II&quot;), complete with soft-focus graphics &amp; vaguely reverential music (unlike the usual FNC garish graphics &amp; hideous musical &quot;themes&quot;) &amp; lots of video of Swiss Guards, St Peter&apos;s (inside the basilica, outside in the square), the 2-mile-long lines of people waiting, etc. There were interviews with a variety of people. Big surprise: everybody loved the Pope....</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5803@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Special Report w/Brit Hume</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-05T14:18:07-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>War Montage Disrespectful To A Man Of Peace</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/04/war_montage_disrespectful_to_a_man_of_peace.php</link>
			<description>Hannity &amp; Colmes tonight was devoted to honoring the Pope and his contributions and until the last 10 minutes, the show was in good taste. The last segment was devoted to the awarding of the Medal Of Honor to a soldier who had been killed in Iraq and Ollie North was on hand to provide some over the top patriotic zeal.Considering the Pope&apos;s stand on the Iraq War, was it really the right thing to do? 4/04/05...</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5802@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Hannity &amp; Colmes</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-04T22:48:31-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>John Gibson Uses The Pope&apos;s Death To Make Political Hay</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/04/john_gibson_uses_the_popes_death_to_make_political_hay.php</link>
			<description>We knew this was coming and there will probably be more examples before the Pope is buried. On tonight&apos;s Big Story, John Gibson used an interview with Thomas Melady, former US Ambassador to the Vatican to score points for the GOP and against the Democrats. Gbison started off the interview by asking the &quot;Big question: How did the Pope use faith to make a political impact?&quot; But the real question in Gibson&apos;s mind was, evidently, how can we use the Pope to make the GOP look good?...</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5801@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Big Story w/John Gibson</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-04T21:49:47-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Five Minutes for Michael Jackson, Zero Time for Tom DeLay</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/04/five_minutes_for_michael_jackson_zero_time_for_tom_delay.php</link>
			<description>House Majority Leader Tom DeLay&apos;s popularity has slipped dramatically as allegations of ethics transgressions continue to swirl around him. Even Dick Cheney characterized DeLay&apos;s behavior as inappropriate when he called for retribution against judges who refused to reinsert Terri Schiavo&apos;s feeding tube. yet today&apos;s Big Story devoted five full minutes to the Michael Jackson trial and zero time to Tom DeLay&apos;s decline. Big Question: Which story is more &quot;real journalism?&quot;...</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5800@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Big Story w/John Gibson</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-04T21:21:00-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Neil Cavuto Misstates (or Lies About) Pope John Paul II&apos;s Position on Iraq</title>
			<link>http://www.newshounds.us/2005/04/04/neil_cavuto_misstates_or_lies_about_pope_john_paul_iis_position_on_iraq.php</link>
			<description>Neil Cavuto (I&apos;ll be generous, for now) vastly misstated Pope John Paul II&apos;s position on the Iraq war today (April 4, 2005) on Your World w/Neil Cavuto. Hussein Ibish of the American-Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee was a guest. (Fox identified him as being from the &quot;Progressive Muslim Unit,&quot; whatever that is.) Hussein was speaking about Pope John Paul&apos;s pacifism and about his frequent support for people on both sides of an issue....</description>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">5799@http://www.newshounds.us/</guid>
			<dc:subject>Cavuto/&amp; Your World</dc:subject>
			<dc:date>2005-04-04T19:06:19-05:00</dc:date>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
